* 
* |

* 

SITE123 Privacy
===============

Effective Date: January 17, 2024
--------------------------------

**1\. Introduction**
====================

At SITE123, safeguarding the privacy of our visitors and users is our top priority. This Privacy Policy outlines how SITE123 (hereafter referred to as “we”, “us”, or “our”), collects, processes, and shares your Personal Information. It also details the rights you have concerning your Personal Information. This policy applies to all who interact with SITE123, whether you're a casual visitor, a registered member, or a premium subscriber (collectively termed “Users”, “you”, or “your”), encompassing all that SITE123 provides: from our primary and secondary websites like www.site123.com ("Website") to our online utilities ("SITE123 Tools") and related offerings (e.g., digital cards, domains, mailboxes - collectively termed “Services”). This Privacy Policy doesn’t overwrite any terms of agreements you might hold with us or any rights you may have under applicable data privacy laws.

We urge you to meticulously read this policy before utilizing our Services to grasp how we handle your Personal Information. If you don't concur with our practices after reading this Privacy Policy, please cease using our Services immediately. For any inquiries or concerns about this policy, you're welcome to contact us at [privacy@site123.com](mailto:privacy@site123.com).

**2\. What We Collect**
=======================

###   
**2.1 Data You Share With Us**

When you register for our Services, attend any of our events, subscribe to our blogs or newsletters, purchase or register domain names, use any of our Services, or directly contact us through any communication channel (e.g., our support tickets, emails), you might provide us with Personal Information. This can include:

* Your name
* Email address
* Phone number
* Payment details (for Users with Paid Services)
* Contents of communication with us and with other users on our platform
* Personal Information from scanned identification documents, such as ID cards, driver’s licenses, passports, or official company registration papers.

### **2.2 Service Usage Data Collection**

Whenever you visit, download, or use any of our services, we gather aggregated usage Personal Information. This consists of your browsing and 'click-stream' activities on the Services, session heatmaps, scrolls, non-identifying details regarding your device, and more:

* OS details
* Internet browser type
* Screen resolution
* Language and keyboard settings
* Internet service provider
* Referring/exit pages
* Date/time stamps, etc.

As you navigate through our platform, specific data accumulates. This encompasses your interactions with our system, purchased or engaged services, viewed advertisements and pages, and services or offers that catch your attention. This data is handled meticulously following the stipulations stated in this Privacy Policy.

### **2.3 Data from Collaborative Sources**

Sometimes, we obtain Personal Information about you from third-party sources. These sources include security providers with whom we collaborate to screen out users associated with fraudulent activities. Additionally, when you sign up or log in using a social media account, we may gather information from that platform, like your username or basic profile details. We also work closely with advertising and marketing partners to manage, measure, and monitor our advertising efforts, and this collaboration can result in us receiving user-related data from these partners to improve our services.

### **2.4 Browser and Server Interactions**

When accessing our site, our servers might automatically document standard data sent by your web browser. This could comprise:

* Your IP address
* The type of browser you use
* The pages you explore and more.

### **2.5 Device Data**

Information regarding the device you're using could be gathered, including:

* Device type
* Operating system
* Unique device identifiers
* Other pertinent device-related details.

### **2.6 Identifying Information**

Certain data we collect can identify you directly. Such data is only collected when you're actively engaging with our services—like registering, utilizing platform features, subscribing, or purchasing. This information is employed exclusively within the context of enhancing or delivering these services. Examples include:

* Name
* Email
* Social media handles
* Date of birth
* Phone or mobile number
* Physical or mailing address
* Transactional data
* Business Information

As users interact with our platform, various data builds up. This encompasses transaction histories, stored files, user profiles, analytical insights, and other metrics. All this data stems from the natural interactions users have with our services.

**3\. Why We Collect**
======================

Our main objective in collecting your personal information is to offer you seamless access to various sections of our website, manage your subscription billing, and keep you informed about alterations to your account and the services we offer.

Additionally, we might reach out using your contact details to share updates regarding our platform, as well as curated content that aligns with your interests. Should you prefer not to receive such promotional messages, there's always the option to unsubscribe by following the instructions in the promotional emails we send.

We employ a mix of both specific and generalized data to delve deeper into understanding our user base – discerning how they interact with our platform and identifying potential avenues for enhancement. These insights not only provide us with a clearer picture of our audience's preferences and the popularity of our offerings but also gauge the success rate of our marketing strategies. While we refrain from revealing this specific data, we might disclose a generalized version that does not pinpoint individual users, like in the form of trend analyses. The essence of collecting this information is to constantly refine our platform, ensuring that we cater to your unique needs and preferences. In summary, we gather information to:

* Analyze user behaviors and demographics
* Elevate the overall user journey on our site
* Recommend tailored content and services
* Update our audience on the latest offerings and promotional content
* Seamlessly execute transactions and deliver our services.

**4\. How We Collect**
======================

We collect information by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used. You are free to refuse our request for this information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some or all of your desired services without it.

**5\. Disclosure of Personal Information**
=============================================

While we integrate third-party services for various needs such as analytics, user authentication, and advertising, we prioritize safeguarding your personal details. Unless you grant us explicit permission, identifying information remains confidential. On occasion, to enhance our services, external consultants may be granted limited access to our data. Yet, we remain firm in our commitment to not share your information with unrelated parties, barring specific scenarios like court orders or potential legal repercussions stemming from your activities within our system. In such situations, the data may be disclosed in line with a court mandate or to parties alleging harm.

For analytical and service improvement purposes, we might grant select external consultants and agencies restricted access to our data. This access is always time-bound and task-specific. We ensure collaborations are only with entities whose privacy practices resonate with ours. Moreover, entities handling payment processing might interact with our data strictly for task completion. We neither provide them any personally identifiable information without your clear approval nor allow them to use our data for other intentions.

In cases where government or law enforcement agencies request data, we critically evaluate the relevance and scope of such demands. If a request appears overly broad or misaligned with its declared objective, we may deny it. Nonetheless, if complying is deemed necessary—for instance, to uphold legal mandates, safeguard our rights and assets, protect public safety, deter crime, or avert potential illegal or unethical conduct—we may cooperate. Outside these contexts, we firmly refrain from sharing, selling, or renting your personal details to any third party or marketers.

Before collaborating with any third-party provider, a thorough review of their privacy protocols is undertaken. We strictly engage with those whose standards align with ours, ensuring you're never unknowingly exposed to services that might jeopardize your privacy.

**6\. Location and Management of Your 'Personal Information'**
==============================================================

The personal information we gather is primarily stored and processed in the United States, but it may also reside in locations where our partners, affiliates, or third-party providers operate. Given our role as a global website builder platform, it's possible for your data to be transferred to, and accessed from, various international locales. Regardless of where the data resides, our dedication to its security and your privacy remains unwavering.

We strictly transfer data across regions that have data protection regulations aligning with our dedication to safeguarding our users' privacy.

Our practice is to retain personal and business information only as long as it's essential for service delivery or for future service enhancements. Throughout its retention, we employ commercially viable means to safeguard the data against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, it's pertinent to note that no electronic storage or transmission method is entirely foolproof. While we strive for optimal data security, we cannot assure its invulnerability. We only keep personal data for as long as necessary for our services or its improvement.

**7\. End-Users’ 'Personal Information'**
=========================================

As a website proprietor, you have an obligation to clearly communicate to your visitors how their data is being handled on your site. When incorporating third-party applications or services, it's crucial to verify their compliance with GDPR. Specifically, if you integrate any applications or services, such as those from our app market \[https://www.site123.com/app-market\], it falls on you to ensure they meet GDPR standards (https://gdpr-info.eu). Furthermore, it's essential to disclose to your users how these third-party tools might process their data.

To align with emerging requirements, we recommend incorporating a comprehensive Privacy Policy on your website.

**8\. Cookies**
===============

###   
**8.1 General**

Our platform utilizes cookies and tracking technologies to enrich your browsing experience. These instruments are pivotal in analyzing how users interact with our website, delivering tailored content, and facilitating user-specific preferences.

Cookies are small data pieces that our website deposits onto your device, which are then accessed every time you revisit. This mechanism allows us to discern your preferences and cater content accordingly. By using our site, you are engaging with our Cookie Policy as embedded within our privacy policy. Although our policy addresses the cookies we set, third-party services linked to our site might also employ cookies; however, they fall outside the purview of our directive.

### **8.2 Understanding What a Cookie Does**

Whenever you visit a website, it may store a unique identifier in the form of a cookie on your device. This identifier, in essence, helps the website recognize your browser on subsequent visits. Beyond just identification, cookies have diverse roles - they enable specific functionalities (like logging in), track site interactions (for analytics), save user settings (like timezone preferences), and even tailor content delivery (like targeted ads).

Cookies issued by the site you're on are "first-party cookies" and primarily monitor your interactions on that specific website. Meanwhile, "third-party cookies" are set by external entities and might track your activities across multiple websites.

### **8.3 Categories of Cookies and Their Utilization on Our Site**

**Essential Cookies:** These are integral for a seamless website experience, facilitating core operations like user sign-ins, account handling, and payments. Our platform employs these cookies for various functionalities.

**Performance Cookies:** These cookies anonymously capture how you navigate our website. Aggregating this data provides insights into user behavior, helping us identify potential issues and optimize the user experience. Both first-party and third-party services might set these cookies on our site.

**Functionality Cookies:** These capture details about your device and your chosen settings on the site (e.g., language preferences). Such information aids websites in offering a more tailored browsing experience. Our site uses these cookies for specific features.

**Targeting/Advertising Cookies:** These cookies streamline the promotional content you see based on your interests. They enhance campaign effectiveness and refine the quality of advertisements. While our website uses these cookies, note that third-party services might also set them, potentially tracking your behavior across various sites.

### **8.4 Third-party Cookies on Our Site**

We collaborate with third-party entities, such as analytics providers, to enhance our site's offerings. While these partners have our permission to access specific information, they may also employ their cookies. As their cookies are beyond our control, they're not encompassed by our cookie policy.

### **8.5 Managing Your Cookie Preferences**

By registering for our services and continuing to use them, you automatically and knowingly agree to accept all our cookies. Most web browsers are configured to accept cookies by default. It's essential to understand that the functionality and performance of our platform rely on these cookies. If you wish to avoid accepting our cookies, the only option is to refrain from using our services.

### **8.6 Notices and Updates from Our End**

We may utilize your personal details to provide you with updates about our services, share promotional content tailored to your interests, or for other reasons that, at our sole discretion, we deem relevant to you. Your contact information ensures that you are kept abreast of important updates, announcements, and other communications we believe are pertinent to your engagement with our services.

**9\. Managing Your Personal Data: Your Rights**
================================================

You possess specific rights regarding the personal data we hold about you. These include the ability to view, update, or request the deletion of your data. Should you decide to have your personal information removed or if it no longer serves a valid purpose in our operations, we commit to deleting it from our systems in a timely manner.

It is your right to be fully informed about the nature and purpose of the data we collect and how we process it. You can access, correct, and update your personal details using the tools available in your account control panel. Additionally, you have the authority to limit our use of your data, while also preserving the capability to utilize your personal data for your own reasons. Moreover, you hold the right to decline any decision that impacts you based solely on automated data processing.

For Google Calendar data, you can view, update, or delete your data directly through your Google Account settings. You can also contact us to request deletion of any Google Calendar data we may have stored.

**10\. Security**
=================

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. This section outlines our commitment and methods in maintaining the security and integrity of your personal information. While we implement rigorous security protocols to guard against unauthorized access and potential breaches, it's essential to note that no method can guarantee absolute security. Our aim is always to minimize risks and protect your data to the best of our ability.

We apply the same rigorous security measures to Google user data as we do to all other user data we collect and process.

**11\. Third-Party Websites**
=============================

Our website might link to external sites not operated by us. We're not responsible for their content or privacy practices. We didn’t review external sites linked from our website and we are not responsible for their content. A link's presence doesn't indicate our endorsement. Use linked sites at your own risk.

**12\. User Consent**
=====================

Your continued use of our platform implies your consent to the collection, storage, and utilization of your data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Should you require further clarity or have queries pertaining to our privacy practices, we encourage you to reach out to our Privacy team at privacy@site123.com.   
By connecting your Google Calendar to our service, you explicitly consent to our access and use of your Google Calendar data as described in this Privacy Policy.

**13\. Scope of Our Privacy Practices**
=======================================

This policy primarily details how we manage and handle data. While we strive to collaborate with partners, affiliates, and third-party providers that share our dedication to privacy, we cannot guarantee or be held liable for their individual privacy procedures. Furthermore, our website may feature links to other external sites not managed by us. It's crucial to recognize that these sites have their own content and privacy policies, and we are not responsible for their specific practices.

**14\. Policy Revision and Notification**
=========================================

We may occasionally modify this privacy policy. When such changes are made, they will be evident on our privacy policy page. As a user, it's your responsibility to stay updated by frequently reviewing our policy. While we will do our utmost to inform you of significant changes, it's essential to ensure you remain informed by checking our policy page. Your continued use of our site following any updates signifies your acceptance of our amended privacy practices.

We will keep our Privacy Policy and in-product privacy notifications up to date regarding our use of Google user data. Any changes to how we handle Google user data will be promptly reflected in these documents.

**15\. Google Login**
=====================

Our service offers the option to connect with your Google account email to your account in the system. We'll only get your email address from Google.

**16\. Google Calendar Integration**
====================================

Our service offers the option to connect your Google Calendar to your account. When you choose to use this feature:

* We access your Google Calendar data, including event details, dates, and times.
* We use this data to display your calendar events on your account for different use cases like schedule booking and events tool.
* We store your events detail and make a live sync a long you keep the connection active. You can choose to disconnect any time you like.

Our use of Google user data complies with Google's Limited Use requirements. We do not use this data for any purpose other than integrating your calendar with your website as requested by you.You can revoke our access to your Google Calendar data at any time through your Google Account settings or by from your account.

**17\. Google API Services Compliance**
=======================================

SITE123's use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google APIs will adhere to the Google API Services User Data Policy, including the Limited Use requirements.For more information, please visit: [https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy)

**18\. Contacting Us**
======================

Feel free to contact us if you have any concerns or questions about how we handle your data and personal information. For any inquiries or concerns related to this policy or your data, please contact:

**Our Data Controller**  
Privacy Department - privacy@site123.com

**Our Data Protection Officer**  
Privacy Department - privacy@site123.com

Don't wait any longer, create your website today! [Create a website](https://app.site123.com/manager/login/sign_up.php?l=en)

SITE123: built differently, built better.

Product

All Options

Company

 Built with love and passion to allow everyone to say something to the world  
Copyright © 2024 All rights reserved - SITE123  
[Terms](https://www.site123.com/terms) - [Privacy](https://www.site123.com/privacy) - [Abuse](https://www.site123.com/abuse) - [Accessibility](https://www.site123.com/accessibility)

×

#### Want to see a quick demo?

Close [Yes! I want to try](https://app.site123.com/manager/login/sign_up.php?l=en)

More than 1572 SITE123 websites created in NL today!
